<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blue Team on @GrandomThoughts</title>
    <link>https://graysonwalters.com/tags/blue-team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blue Team on @GrandomThoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016-2017 Grayson Walters</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 10:33:50 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://graysonwalters.com/tags/blue-team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Errata Security - How to track that annoying pop-up</title>
      <link>https://graysonwalters.com/post/errata_security_sysmon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 10:33:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graysonwalters.com/post/errata_security_sysmon/</guid>
      <description>My take - Rob at Errata Sec did a concise job of showing how to use sysmon to track down a weird pop-up. This one came from MS Office update. He uses the @SwiftonSecurity sysmon-config that I posted about recently. From the article:
 &amp;ldquo;How to track that annoying pop-up In a recent update to their Office suite on Windows, Microsoft made a mistake where every hour, for a fraction of a second, a black window pops up on the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwiftonSecurity - sysmon-config</title>
      <link>https://graysonwalters.com/post/swiftonsecurity_sysmon-config/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 10:57:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graysonwalters.com/post/swiftonsecurity_sysmon-config/</guid>
      <description>My take - @SwiftonSecurity released a config file for sysmon to help cut through the clutter. There is a steep learning curve with sysmon, so I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t recommend blindly applying this, but it definitely is a good starting point. I&amp;rsquo;ve also included a link below to Lennart Koopmann&amp;rsquo;s take on the config, which explains it a little more. From the article:
 &amp;ldquo;sysmon-config | A Sysmon configuration file for everybody to fork This is a Microsoft Sysinternals Sysmon configuration file template with default high-quality event tracing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Russinovich - Tracking Hackers on Your Network with Sysinternals Sysmon</title>
      <link>https://graysonwalters.com/post/markrussinovich_sysmon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 13:10:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graysonwalters.com/post/markrussinovich_sysmon/</guid>
      <description>My take - @MarkRussinovich did a very good presentation at RSAC covering the use of Sysmon to hunt hackers on your network. From the article:
 &amp;ldquo;Windows Forensic Monitoring Limitations -  When attackers or malware get on your network, you need to  construct a timeline What was the entry point? Did it spread between systems? What happened on a particular system?  Built-in Windows tooling make it hard to answer these questions:  Limited information captured for process creates and DLL loading Network connection information simultaneously too limited and verbose No way to capture common attacker behavior (e.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>